clubshop.com 2005-12-12

# The DHS Club Business Manual - Privacy Policy

**Policies**

**_Privacy Policy_**

We understand that when you are doing business online you need to trust the people with whom you are doing business.  We take this trust very seriously, and make it a priority to ensure the security and confidentiality of the personal information ("PI") you provide us. (PI includes information that can be linked to a specific individual, such as name, address, phone number, or e-mail address.)

Therefore, as a visitor to The DHS Club's web sites clubshop.com, dhs-club.com, you have the right to understand our information privacy policies before  providing the DHS Club with any of your PI.

**What information we collect**   
The DHS Club collects PI that you voluntarily provide to us as well as certain technical information from your computer each time you request a page at the dhs-club.com and clubshop.com sites.  This technical information is collected from your computer's web browser and may include your IP address, operating system, web browser software (i.e. Netscape Navigator or Internet Explorer), screen resolution and referrer web site.

**How we use your information**  
The DHS Club may use your personal information for the purpose of responding to and fulfilling your requests for Membership in our Club, for the purchase of products and services and posting at our website locations such as password protected downline reports (name, ID number, email address, mailing address, and phone number) and newsletters (name, ID number, and in some instances city, state, country). 

**Who we share your information with**   
The DHS Club may share your contact information with your originating sponsor or a sponsor assigned to you (name, ID number, email address, mailing address, and phone number) and your upline and/or downline Team for communications (name, ID number and e-mail address) and our authorized product and service providers as necessary in order to complete a transaction that you specifically request.

**How you can control your information**   
The DHS Club provides you with the means of updating or correcting any PI stored in your customer profile.

**Updating your information**   
VIPs may update their personal information at the [VIP Information Update Page  ](https://www.clubshop.com/vip/updateinfo.html). Free Members may update their personal information at the [Free Member Information Update Page](https://www.clubshop.com/m-update.html).  VIPs may update their payment information at the [Payment Update Page](https://www.clubshop.com/cgi/mopi.cgi). Merchants may update their payment information from their Merchant Affiliate site. 

**How we protect your information**   
To ensure the confidentiality of your PI, The DHS Club uses leading security technology and procedures. When you submit personal information on clubshop.com, your data is protected by Secure Socket  Layer (SSL) technology certified by a digital certificate from Thawte Server CA. To view this site certificate on each secured page (a page which begins with "https"), click on the image of the closed lock or the solid key on the bottom bar of your browser window. A small frame displaying site security information will pop up.

By providing you with this Privacy Statement, The DHS Club is pledging our continued commitment to protecting the information you provide us. Your privacy is important to us. Questions regarding this statement should be e-mailed to The DHS Club at [network@dhs-club.com](mailto:network@dhs-club.com) or sent via postal mail The DHS Club, Inc., 2560 Placida Road, Englewood, FL 34224.   

* * *

The DHS Club Privacy Statement   

* * *

This DHS Club Privacy Statement discloses the information privacy practices for The DHS Club's United States web sites, www.dhs-club.com, www.clubshop.com and www.clubbucks.com. A DHS Club membership may be available to residents of the U.S. and foreign countries that are of the legal age of consent in their country/state/province. Membership by individuals not of the legal age of consent is prohibited.

**Information collected about you**   
The DHS Club collects Personal information ("PI") about you that you specifically and voluntarily provide. PI includes information that can identify you as a specific individual, such as, but not limited to, your name, address, phone number, or e-mail address.  The DHS Club collects your Member ID, name, city, state, country/province, postal code when you initially register to become a member of our Club.

**Use of your information**   
Information collected by The DHS Club may be used to:

  * Register you as a DHS Club Member or Shopper and/or activate a ClubBucks Rewards Card
  * Purchase products or services at your request
  * Send e-mail notifications
  * Respond to your questions or suggestions
  * Notify your sponsor and upline and/or downline Team of your Membership in the DHS Club
  * Post your name, ID#, email address, mailing address, and phone number on your VIP sponsor's password protected network and genealogy reports
  * Post your name, ID# and email address on your upline VIPs password protected network and genealogy reports
  * Post your name, ID#, and city/state/country on the Den Report and International Den Report
  * Respond to a Spam complaint against you or your email address

**VIP or Merchant profile information and purchase information**   
The DHS Club collects information relative to the credit and/or debit card or checking account  that is being used to purchase a VIP ClubAdvantage Membership Subscription, register a Merchant Affiliate or purchase a product or service from our Outlet and Benefit Centers. This information includes the name and address of the card holder and, if the card holder is a subscriber to the ClubAdvantage Benefits Program (a VIP) the name, address, phone number, social security number or federal id number (if applicable), email address of the card holder for the initial subscription fee and monthly subscription fees (if applicable). If the card holder is a Merchant Affiliate, we will collect the name, address, phone, social security number, FEIN, email address and all card holder information. If a VIP ClubAdvantage Membership subscription is purchased with a credit and/or debit card or checking account of an individual who is not a registered DHS Club VIP/Member, we will collect the name, address, email address of that individual as provided.

**Cookies and other Web technologies**   
As a Member visiting password protected areas of the DHS Club or ClubShop.com site you will be assigned a cookie which identifies you as a DHS Club member. You may learn more about cookies [here](http://www.clubshop.com/manual/technical/cookie_help.html). You can always choose to not receive a cookie file by enabling your Web browser to refuse cookies or prompt you before accepting a cookie. Learn how to do this [here](http://www.clubshop.com/manual/technical/cookiesetup.html). Be advised that, by refusing to accept a cookie, you will not be able to access the password protected areas of the DHS Club or ClubShop.com sites.

When you access the [Control Center ](http://www.clubshop.com/vip/control/index.html) or other password protected areas of the DHS Club or ClubShop.com,  we require you to sign in using your Member ID and password (or Merchant ID, Password and location ID). Free Members must supply their ID Number or ClubBucksRewards ID Number to access their [Personal Line Reports](http://www.clubshop.com/ppreport.html). Once you sign in as a Member or Merchant Affiliate, we record the Member or Merchant ID and the Member's or Merchant's password in a [cookie](http://www.clubshop.com/manual/technical/cookie_help.html) in your browser. Your Member ID and password or Merchant ID and password are stored in the cookie as encrypted data, so no one can view the information it contains by obtaining unauthorized access to your computer. This cookie is erased when you log out of the Control Center or other password protected areas if you close down your browser or after 12 hours, whichever comes first. 

**Our Affiliates**   
The DHS Club has partnered with reputable third parties to offer our Members and site visitors a variety of products and services. Although we only work with reputable third parties, our business partners may have different privacy policies and practices than The DHS Club. We encourage you to review our business partners' privacy policies to further understand their procedures for collecting, using, and disclosing your information.

**E-mail notifications**   
All Members except Shoppers in the DHS Club will receive periodic communications via e-mail from DHS Club HQ as well as from their sponsor and/or upline regarding our business opportunities. All Members will receive periodic communications via e-mail from the DHS Club HQ as well as from their sponsor and/or upline regarding our consumer opportunities. 

**Responses to your questions or suggestions**   
We will use your e-mail address or telephone number to respond to you when you submit an email or telephone question or request assistance with viewing your account.

**Product or Service providers**   
We will provide a Member's PI (to include their name, address, phone number, credit card or checking information)  to a product or service provider of the DHS Club Outlet Center or ClubShop Mall or ClubShop Marketplace affiliate store when this information  is necessary in order to complete an order for products or services.

**Our legal obligations**   
The DHS Club may be required by law to disclose information you have provided in obtaining our products or services. The DHS Club may also disclose information against someone who poses a threat to The DHS Club's interests (such as customer fraud) or whose activities could bring harm to others.

**Other Web sites**   
There are places throughout The DHS Club website (www.clubshop.com and www.dhs-club.com)  that may link you to other web sites that do not operate under The DHS Club's information privacy practices. When you click through to these web sites, The DHS Club's information privacy practices no longer apply. We recommend that you examine the privacy statements for all third-party Web sites to understand their procedures for collecting, using, and disclosing your information.  These third party websites include, but are not limited to ClubShop Mall affiliate stores, VIP Benefits and International VIP Benefits Centers providers and vendors.

**Changes to The DHS Club Privacy Statement**   
This Privacy Statement was originally produced and posted on The DHS Club's site on March 6, 2002. This policy was amended on November 26, 2003 and notification of this amendment was posted on our website. The DHS Club reserves the right to modify or amend this Privacy Statement at any time and for any reason. If you have questions about our Privacy Statement, please email us at network@dhs-club.com  

[ Top ]
